So I'm coming out the airport today and TMZ stopped me.
It's a British guy, a British reporter.
And he's like, Amanda, you know, I'd love to talk to you about Palestine, about Palestine.
Now y'all know I'm going to talk about Palestine.
So I said, fine.
However, I didn't know that they was going to do this.
Insecure star Amanda Seals calls Biden evil for Gaza-Israel policy.
I did not say that.
I want y'all to listen to what I said and see how they twisted my shit.
For you personally, has Biden lost your vote because of things he's done and things he hasn't done for Palestinian people?
He's definitely lost my confidence.
That's for damn sure.
I mean, at the end of the day, I am not in any position to tell people how to vote or where to vote or in terms of him losing my vote.
Ultimately, none of these politicians are really winning anyone's vote.
They're just kind of possibly getting it by nature of choosing the lesser of two evils.
And if I was a human being, well, I am a human being.
And as I am a human being and I was running for office, I personally would hate for someone to be voting me because I'm the lesser of two evils.
That means I'm still an evil.
Right, right.
So what should he do then if you were the president?
What should he do?
If I were the president, in third grade, I said I would be the first black female president of the United States of America.
I'm sure Kamala's like, ah, ah, ah.
I think on a basic note, the president can do exactly what Mehdi Hassan said he could do and listen to the majority of the American people who have made it abundantly clear that they want to see a ceasefire.
They want to see Palestinians no longer under the threat of death for literally just being Palestinian.
And we also want to see a number of other things, like Biden actually just listening to us on the subject of education, on the subject, you know, we really want to see him stand up against the Republicans.
That's what we really want to see.
Right.
We want to see an actual difference that is a chasm, not a half step.
Now, I know y'all are like, Amanda, what would you expect from TMZ?
Obviously, they were going to twist your shit.
But I had specifically said, do not let my words get twisted.
And he said, oh, well, I'm not going to do it.
No, I've got you.
I've got you.
So, Harvey, I bid you adieu.
That's my last TMZ interview because I really cannot believe that y'all went that far to put those kind of words in my mouth in that way because that is such a misrepresentation of what I was trying to say.
And y'all be playing with people's lives.
I don't like it.
Free Palestine.